# **GEORGII SHYRIAIEV**

### **PROFILE**

Hello, I am a front-end developer with experience in web development, specializing in HTML, CSS, and JavaScript. I also have experience working with PHP, WordPress, Laravel, Tailwind, React, Rest API, and Gulp.

I enjoy creating clean, elegant, and straightforward code that provides better user interaction and understanding. I always strive to help with the development of better web applications, ensuring code validation and debugging with debugging tools, as well as providing feedback and thorough project analysis.

I value openness and friendliness in the team because it helps us achieve better results and develop as professionals. I am ready for a challenge because I always aim to improve my skills and become a better front-end developer.

### **TECHNOLOGY STACK**

- PHP (Laravel, WordPress, HumHub);
- HTML/CSS,
- JS ES6 (ReactJS, VueJS)
- SASS, LESS;
- Gulp, Grunt;
- Git;
- NodeJS, MongoDB, Firebase, SQL

## **EXPERIENCE**

Mencodehard. (Remotely)
Position: Frontend engineer.

- Freelance. 03.2022 - 08.2022

- WebLoveMe. *Dnipro* **09.2021-02.2022** 

*Position: Trainee Frontend developer.* 

## **EDUCATION**

National university of telecommunications, Bachelor. *Kyiv. 2012-2015* College of radio electronics, Junior Specialist. *Dnipro. 2008-2012* 

#### **COURSES**

Script Jedi 42, deep study of javascript. Online. 2021

Softserve, HTML/CSS/JS Fundamentals. Online. 2021

Skillup, software testing. Dnipro. 2015

ITStep, Web-development and SEO. Dnipro. 2013-2014